Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in what I do.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't wanna live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We believe in one another.
Luffy, help!
There isn't much time left
until the square is blown up!
Everyone is already down there.
My voice can't, it can't be
heard, no matter how loud I yell.
At this rate, the country will fall apart.
Don't worry, Vivi.
As long as we're here, your
voice will always be heard.
I'm telling you again!
My injuries are a whole lot
more severe than yours are.
Oh, quit whining and act like a man!
My leg is hurt, so I can't stand.
I'm gonna bleed!
You are such a liar.
Best of luck, Luffy.
Be careful.
I ate tons of meat, bird guy.
I'll be just fine.
I won't lose to you.
How did he make it out of the
quicksand with all his injuries?
It's Luffy, he's alive!
Tony's here too!
What? Luffy! Luffy!
And Vivi's here too!
See? See?
He's still alive!
What did I tell you?
I knew it all along! Really?
For someone who knew it all
along, you sure look surprised.
Usopp, Sanji, you're alright!
Vivi, what happened? Are you okay?
You look like you've been hurt!
Nami, too? And Mr. Bushido?
Everyone is alive.
Usopp, who asked you to create
some useless Park for parties?
Oh, come on!
You're standing up just fine!
Nami, my love!
Well, it did have a powerful
attack, right, Nami?
Just shut up!
I'm going to deal with you later!
Phoebe?
What's going on?
What's up with all this
dust flying everywhere?
Explain yourself, idiot.
How could you let Nami
get injured like that?
What happened?
She's fine. Let it go.
Listen, Jumper.
Do me a favor.
Bury my body out of the
wastelands when I'm dead and gone.
No, Zab, don't die!
I'm sorry, you guys.
I know I lost to him once already.
This time...
I'm gonna win!
The rest is up to you!
So get going already.
If you can't beat this guy, then
I don't know anybody who can!
I'm gonna put an end to this.
For good!
After all this happened, all
of you are still with me.
Crocodile!
Try all you want, but no matter how many
times you swing, you'll never hit me.
I guess you didn't get
enough the first time, huh?
What the? Who's that?
How can he hit me?
My son!
He hit Crocodile!
Get up!
I figured something out when some of
my Yuba water dropped on your hand.
Once you touch water, then you
can't turn into sand anymore.
You took away all the rain because
you're afraid of water, didn't you?
I know how to defeat you, crocodile.
Our real fight is starting now!
Are you serious?
In ten minutes, this place
is really going to blow up?
In ten minutes!
But how do we find him?
Well, not by standing around here.
But if everything in this
area is going to explode,
then the cannon guy has to
be far away, doesn't he?
Or else he'd just blow
up with the rest of it.
No way. No. He's close.
The cannoneer is almost
certainly near the palace square.
What?
Are you serious, Vivi?
But that means he's gonna be
caught in the explosion, too.
I guess that shouldn't be too surprising.
It is crocodile
He's just playing evil come on let's go.
Looks like we found you
princess i wonder how
big a promotion crocodile
would give us for
killing you billions it
looks like we'll lose
some time he's right so
let's not waste all of it
Jabra jabbering let's
go i'll go ahead yeah
your counting is not
helping let's split up we
need to get out of this
dust devil if we're gonna
find anything ten minutes
all right now let's
go hurry yeah this is
really it this is the
last chance in ten
minutes the country's fate
could be decided we're good
come
on you think
you can defeat me sure do
i'll admit i'm impressed
you figured it out
especially since you were
about to die but i hope
you realize something like
that isn't nearly enough
to make this an even
fight i am one of the
seven warlords of the sea
so what if you're one of the seven dumb
warlords i guess that
makes me the eighth warlord
really who is that guy he's a pirate i'm
surprised you haven't heard about him yet
he's helped your darling princess vivi
escape from death a few times now?
So then he is the one responsible
for bringing Vivi back?
If I got it, then it's no use.
My hand can still absorb any fluid on you.
For that matter, my hand can absorb
all the water in your body as well.
Oh crap, forgot about that trick!
Alright, not bad
Remember how you told me Devil-free
powers Get stronger Gong-gong-pista
Shotgun!
That stupid heart doesn't bother!
Uh-oh!
Just barely.
Now Gum-Gum!
You just keep using the
same move against me.
Do you wanna win? Yeah!
And I'm going to!
That's been my plan from the beginning!
Time for you to get wet!
Of course, your plan
was out here. Save us!
Barrel!
You're struggling so
hard, Straw Hat Luffy.
You can't do anything at all without
that barrel of yours, now can you?
this isn't any different
from my first fight
against you after all yeah
you're right crocodile it
isn't any different like
this
how
about now I'm
not the same as i was huh
you gotta be kidding me
water luffy oh no a leak you
can't be serious about this
can he
i guess i shouldn't
have drunk that much water
does this idiot really not
understand what's going on here
Damn it, stop your messing around!
Damn them, brat!
Who said I was messing around?
My body!
I'm always serious! Let me show you!
Now, Gum-Gum!
How is that?
Sand Krieg.
That's amazing.
He beat Crocodile?
There's no time now for
all this admiration.
We have other things to do.
Get up.
It's time for us to get moving.
You are going to show me
the way to the Poneglyph.
What are you planning to do?
How could looking at it possibly help you?
Just stop asking questions.
All you have to do is show me where it is.
Your luck's beginning to run out.
You certainly did try, but
there's not much time left.
You should get going now, Nico Robber.
Unless you want to be dried
up along with this brat.
Go. Now.
I'm done playing games.
Nico Robin?
Yes.
As you wish.
Listen up, Straw Hat.
I'm going to destroy every
last rock on this ground.
And you alone with them.
Oh, the grass is dying!
Grounds echo!
Falling!
Oh, that was close. All right.
Water, water.
His hand sucked it up.
You actually thought you could
kill my powers, didn't you?
Water, Luffy.
That was a very foolish mistake to make.
The true power of sand is
trying things out. Watch.
My right hand can suck the life out
of anything by turning it to dust.
Its power is limitless.
It wasn't exaggerating.
Even the statues are crumbling.
Everything is just dying.
My sandal!
Everything that is connected
to the ground is done for.
Including you.
Ground dead!
What impeccable timing you marines
have, showing up right now.
Get out of the way.
We're in a hurry. No chance.
Thanks to one of the soldiers,
I know everything that's been
going on here in Alubarna.
We're not moving.
That man, do you have any idea who he is?
Yes, and I don't care.
I'm not listening to him, you, or
anyone else from the government.
And I would strongly recommend that
you and your men get out of my way.
We have no intention of giving way to you.
Well then, you may not live much longer.
Please hold on!
Don't be worried about me!
We've been warned that at
4.30 a bomb is going to be
shot into the Palace Square
where the fighting's going on!
Please, you have to go stop it now!
That's only minutes from now if
this attack happens it'll cost
a million citizens their lives
well all right we'll save you and
then we'll stop the attack wait
you don't know who she is move
out of my way Prank that mirror
a Devil Fruit I said I was in a
hurry didn't I don't make me angry
with you that's her it's really
nicole robin i'm sure of it i
looked up her old wanted poster
because captain smoker had asked
me to do so that's really her
she has a bounty 20 years ago the
whole world was talking about her
i still remember the articles
that appeared in the newspaper
around that time in a terrifying
incident six marine warships
were destroyed they said that
an eight-year-old girl was
responsible for sinking them the
government classified her as a first
-degree risk and they put an
incredible bounty on her head 79
million berries it's still an amazing
sum after that she just suddenly
disappeared stop your pointless
rambling either move out of my
way or you're all dead okay it's useless
having this many soldiers. Never spied her.
Sergeant, take the men and head to
the square to stop the explosion!
But Sergeant Major!
Just do it!
There's only minutes left! Right!
Now, let that man go right away!
I've already warned you to move.
That was bad.
That right hand of his is
gonna be a big problem.
The entire lawn has been
turned into a desert.
Oh great!
Ready go now!
I'm quite tired of
wasting my time with you.
Missed me.
You have lost to me two times now.
Straw Hat, Luffy.